Guide to the Carlyle Marney Papers, 1899-1979 RL.00848
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence Series, circa 1945-1978
  - Haynsworth, J.E., 1975 (Box 22)
  - Heard, Wyatt H., 1971 (Box 23)
  - Heaton, George, 1958-1976 (Box 23)
  - Heinsohn, Edmond, 1966-1977 (Box 23)
  - Helms, Fred, 1958-1977 (Box 23)
  - Helms, Fred and Teddy - a Book. (Box 23)
  - Helper, Cedric, 1968-1972 (Box 23)
  - Helvey, James Jr., 1958-1966 (Box 23)
  - Henderson, Martha, 1971-1974 (Box 23)
  - Henderson, Wendell, 1959-1973 (Box 23)
  - Hendricks, Louise, 1949-1964 (Box 23)
  - Henley, Carl, 1965-1966 (Box 23)
  - Henry, Al, 1967 (Box 23)
  - Herrman, Ratheryn, 1960-1961 (Box 23)
  - Hicks, Bryant and Peggy, 1960 (Box 23)
  - Higdon, Joe and Margo, 1960-1971 (Box 23)
  - Higgins, Al S., 1959-1964 (Box 24)
  - Higgins, Pecos, 1958-1975 (Box 24)
  - High, Kermit, 1963-1965 (Box 24)
  - Hildreth, Betty, 1962 (Box 24)
  - Hill, William, 1960-1961 (Box 24)
  - Hobbs, H.H., 1964-1972 (Box 24)
  - Hobbs, Ramelle (and family), 1961-1973 (Box 24)
  - Holcomb, Luther, 1958-1965 (Box 24)
  - Holcomb, Walter L., 1962-1965 (Box 24)
  - Holland, Lang Floyd, 1958-1973 (Box 24)
  - Holland, Paul L., 1975 (Box 24)
  - Hollifield, Howard and Nina, 1963-1969 (Box 24)
  - Hollingshead, Frederick, 1969-1971 (Box 24)
  - Hollis, Harry (and family), 1959-1977 (Box 24)
  - Holt, Frosty, 1959-1967 (Box 24)
  - Bolt, Rinehart, and Winston Publishers, 1962-1963 (Box 24)
  - Hopkin, Wade, 1966-1967 (Box 24)
  - Hard, Robert, 1959-1960 (Box 24)
  - Home, Chevis, 1959-1975 (Box 24)
  - Horton, Daisy, 1960-1967 (Box 24)
  - Hovde, Howard, 1960-1977 (Box 24)
  - Howard, Rev. Robert, 1958-1977 (Box 24)
  - Howe, Reuel L., 1961-1973 (Box 24)
  - Howie, Ann Rivers, 1958-1969 (Box 24)
  - Hawser, Phil, 1959-1964 (Box 24)
  - Huddleston, Ed, 1960-1965 (Box 24)
  - Hughes, John, 1958-1976 (Box 24)
  - Hunsicker, David S., 1961-1966 (Box 24)
  - Hunter, James, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
  - Huntley, Hugh, 1965-1971 (Box 24)
  - Hurt, John J., 1958-1967 (Box 24)
  - I, 1958-1978 (Box 25)
  - Illness of others, 1958 (Box 25)
  - In the Meantime (Pastoral Preaching) 1962-1972 (Box 25)
  - Ivey, George and Mrs., 1958-1974 (Box 25)
  - Ivy, Quenton, 1962-1966 (Box 25)
  - Ja-Jom, 1958-1976 (Box 25)
  - Jon-Jz, 1959-1978 (Box 25)
  - Jackson, Gordon, 1964 (Box 25)
  - Jackson, Herbert, 1961-1968 (Box 25)
  - Jackson, Rhett, 1971-1977 (Box 25)
  - Jefferies, Patty, 1967 (Box 25)
  - Jefferies, William, 1967-1973 (Box 25)
  - Job, Rueben, 1968 (Box 25)
  - John Knox Press, 1963-1966 (Box 25)
  - Johnson, Ben, 1976-1977 (Box 25)
  - Johnson C. Smith, 1964-1966 (Box 25)
  - Johnson, Claudia, 1964-1965 (Box 25)
  - Johnson, Lyndon Baines, 1962-1965 (Box 25)
  - Johnson, L. D., 1962-1978 (Box 25)
  - Johnson, Mordecai, 1968-1978 (Box 25)
  - Johnson, Rev. Robert, 1970-1978 (Box 25)
  - Jones, Brooks, 1971-1978 (Box 25)
  - Jones, Curtis, 1963-1976 (Box 25)
  - Jones, Hunter, 1959-1972 (Box 25)
  - Jones, Ithel, 1964-1966 (Box 25)
  - Jones, Robert L,, 1963-1967 (Box 25)
  - Jones, Toni, 1970-1978 (Box 25)
  - Jones, Wilbur, 1959-1975 (Box 25)
  - Jordan, Clarence, 1965-1969 (Box 26)
  - Judson Press, 1961-1976 (Box 26)
  - Junker, Bill, 1959-1966 (Box 26)
  - Justice, Willa, 1962-1967 (Box 26)
  - Ka-Kh, 1954-1975 (Box 26)
  - Ki-Kn, 1958-1976 (Box 26)
  - Ko-Kz, 1958-1976 (Box 26)
  - Kanoy, Robert C., 1960-1976 (Box 26)
  - Kates, Frederick Ward, 1959-1973 (Box 26)
  - Kaufman, R.F., 1959 (Box 26)
  - Kellam, J.C., 1954-1974 (Box 26)
  - Kenderick, Deborah, 1973-1976 (Box 26)
  - Kennedy, Dewitt, 1959-1967 (Box 26)
  - Kennedy, Linwood, 1967 (Box 26)
  - Kilgore, William J., 1958-1978, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Killinger, John, 1964-1971 (Box 27)
  - King, James, 1962-1966 (Box 27)
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr., 1965 (Box 27)
  - Kliever, Lonnie, 1958-1972 (Box 27)
  - Knebel, H. A., 1974-1975 (Box 27)
  - Knight, Monty, 1971-1978 (Box 27)
  - Knott, John, 1958-1969 (Box 27)
  - Kuykendall, Bill and Alice and family, 1958-1970 (Box 27)
  - Kuykendall, F. L. 1958-1968 (Box 27)
  - La-Ld, 1958-1978 (Box 27)
  - Le-Lh, 1958-1978 (Box 28)
  - Li-Lt, 1956-1976 (Box 28)
  - Lu- Lz, 1954-1975 (Box 28)
  - Lake, Katie and Claudine, 1959-1966 (Box 28)
  - Lander, Betty and Bill, 1967-1970 (Box 28)
  - Landes, James H., 1961-1968 (Box 28)
  - Lane, Sue, 1960-1962 (Box 28)
  - Laney, John William, 1960-1961 (Box 28)
  - Laughon, Fred T., 1958-1959 (Box 28)
  - Lawrence, Don and Jerrie, 1958-1974 (Box 28)
  - Laymon, Charles M., 1958-1959 (Box 28)
  - Lee, Maryat, 1965 (Box 28)
  - Leonard, Jonathan, 1968 (Box 28)
  - Lewallen, Betsy Jo, 1960-1967 (Box 28)
  - Lindsay, Rev. Samual M., 1960-1978 (Box 28)
  - Litten, Frank, 1954-1972 (Box 28)
  - Little, Brooks B., 1966-1971 (Box 28)
  - Lord, Fred Townley 1960 (Box 28)
  - Loring, Ed, 1963-1971 (Box 28)
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad Co., 1964 (Box 28)
  - Lovell, Robert, 1958-1974 (Box 28)
  - Lowry, James, 1972-1974 (Box 28)
  - L.Q.C. Lamar Society, 1969-1975 (Box 28)
  - Lucke, Joel, 1962-1969 (Box 28)
  - Lynch, Lorenzo A., 1965-1968 (Box 28)
  - Ma-Mar, 1954-1978 (Box 29)
  - Mas-McC, 1958 -1978 (Box 29)
  - McD-Md, 1954-1978 (Box 29)
  - Me- Mor, 1954-1977 (Box 29)
  - Mos-Mz, 1954-1978 (Box 29)
  - MacLeod, Dr. Donald, 1967-1969 (Box 30)
  - MacMillan, G. I., 1975-1977 (Box 30)
  - Madden, Myron C., 1958-1962 (Box 30)
  - Maddox, Sid, 1961-1973 (Box 30)
  - Madison, J.C., 1964-1969 (Box 30)
  - Malmborg, Hal, 1959-1969 (Box 30)
  - Manley, Jack, 1967-1969 (Box 30)
  - Maples, Rev. Dick, 1970-1975 (Box 30)
  - Marbridge Foundation (J.E. Bridges), 1953-1978 (Box 30)
  - Marney, Pay and Grace, 1958-1972 (Box 30)
  - Marney, Frank and Mary, 1958-1977 (Box 30)
  - Marney, John Leonard and Evelyn, 1954-1964 (Box 30)
  - Marney, John L. (death condolences), 1971 (Box 30)
  - Marney, Milton, 1954-1967 (Box 30)
  - Marney, Milton and Family, 1967-1978 (Box 30)
  - Marney, Rita C. and Susan E., 1962-1964 (Box 30)
  - Marney, Rev. Sam 1973 (Box 30)
  - Marney, Sam R., 1960-1970 (Box 30)
  - Marney, S. Rowe and Frances, 1960-1966 (Box 30)
  - Marney, Wylie, 1965-1968 (Box 30)
  - Mars-Hill College, 1959-1964 (Box 31)
  - Marsh, Lex, 1958-1974 (Box 31)
  - Marsh, William, 1961-1969 (Box 31)
  - Martin, Chris, 1970-1974 (Box 31)
  - Martin, Ed T., 1959-1964 (Box 31)
  - Martin, Grier, 1961-1964 (Box 31)
  - Martin, Tom and Ole Mae, 1958-1978 (Box 31)
  - Mason, David E., 1963-1964 (Box 31)
  - Mathews, E.J.and Ravenna, 1954-1964 (Box 31)
  - Mathews, Ravenna, 1965-1977 (Box 31)
  - Mathias, Fredrirck, 1963-1973 (Box 31)
  - Matthews, Lawerence, 1960-1967 (Box 31)
  - Mays, Benjamin, 1958-1967 (Box 31)
  - McClain, Howard G., 1967-1975 (Box 31)
  - McClernon, Robert E., 1960-1978 (Box 31)
  - McCord, James, 1957-1967 (Box 31)
  - McCracken, Jarrell, 1962-1963 (Box 32)
  - McDonald, Dr. and Dr. Bob (Susan Marney), 1965-1978 (Box 32)
  - McDowell, Arthur G., 1963 (Box 32)
  - Mcdowell, Edward A. 1958-1970 (Box 32)
  - McDowell, Reese, 1958-1971 (Box 32)
  - McFadden, L. A., 1956-1960 (Box 32)
  - McFatridge, F. V., 1960-1967 (Box 32)
  - McHenry, Warren, Mrs., 1965-1967 (Box 32)
  - McIver, Bruce, 1964-1973 (Box 32)
  - McKee, Gil, Mrs., 1967-1973 (Box 32)
  - McRinney, Margaret, 1959-1966 (Box 32)
  - McLeod, Powers, 1968-1975 (Box 32)
  - McMillian, C. L., 1960 (Box 32)
  - McNairy, Mr. and Mrs. Luther, 1958-1965 (Box 32)
  - Menninger, Karl, M. D., 1964-1966 (Box 32)
  - Mikolaski, Samuel, 1964-1966 (Box 32)
  - Milford, Charles, 1963-1978 (Box 32)
  - Miller, A. C., 1958-1973 (Box 32)
  - Miller, Charles E., 1958-1966 (Box 32)
  - Miller, Landon W., 1958-1969 (Box 32)
  - Mobley, Et, 1960-1965 (Box 32)
  - Moncreif, Adiel, 1959-1966 (Box 32)
  - Moody, E. B., 1958-1973 (Box 32)
  - Moody, Howard, 1965 (Box 32)
  - Moore, Author, 1960-1967 (Box 32)
  - Moore, Bernice and Harry, 1959-1960 (Box 32)
  - Moore, Filbert, 1967-1970 (Box 32)
  - Moore, H. Guy, 1958-1969 (Box 32)
  - Moore, Harry E. Jr., 1967-1973 (Box 32)
  - Moore, Harry L., 1966-1967 (Box 32)
  - Moore, Joe S., 1964-1977 (Box 32)
  - Morgan, Martha, 1967 (Box 33)
  - Morikawa, Jitsuo, 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Moses, Mary C., 1958-1962 (Box 33)
  - Moyers, Bill D., 1960-1966 (Box 33)
  - Mueller, William A., 1960-1969 (Box 33)
  - Munger, Bernard V., 1960-1962 (Box 33)
  - Murdock, Al, 1971-1973 (Box 33)
  - Murdock, John A., 1962-1966 (Box 33)
  - Myers, Lewis, 1964-1977 (Box 33)
  - Myers Park Baptist Church, 1958-1967, 2 folders (Box 33)
  - N. 1958-1977 (Box 33)
  - Nail, John G. 1965-1969 (Box 33)
  - National Advisory Commission on Rural Poverty, 1966-1968 (Box 33)
  - National Council of Churches, 1967-1972 (Box 33)
  - Neal, Charles, 1960-1961 (Box 34)
  - Nelson, J. Robert, 1958-1959 (Box 34)
  - Neville, Elsie, 1954-1960 (Box 34)
  - Newelt, Nans Charles, 1963-1965 (Box 34)
  - Newman, Samuel, 1945-1962 (Box 34)
  - Newman, Stewart A., 1959-1966 (Box 34)
  - Newport, John P., 1954-1973 (Box 34)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1959 (Box 34)
  - Noble, Fred, 1958-1963 (Box 34)
  - Norfleet, Frank F., 1958-1967 (Box 34)
  - Norman, T.J., 1958-1971 (Box 34)
  - Norris, Hills Jr., 1967 (Box 34)
  - North Carolina Council on Human Relations, 1968 (Box 34)
  - O. 1958-1977 (Box 34)
  - Old Catawba Society, 1963-1965 (Box 34)
  - Olmedo, Alfonso, 1945-1978, 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Osborn, Bill, 1960-1966 (Box 34)
  - Osborn, Charles A., Jr., 1958-1964 (Box 34)
  - Osborn, Wallace S., 1958-1959 (Box 34)
  - Otto, Robert, 1967-1973 (Box 34)
  - Owens, R. Eugene, 1968-1976 (Box 34)
  - Pa-Pd, 1958-1975 (Box 35)
  - Pe-Pn, 1958-1978 (Box 35)
  - Po-Pz, 1958-1978 (Box 35)
  - Page, Bruce, 1971-1975 (Box 35)
  - Pappas, Evelyn Moss, 1964-1965 (Box 35)
  - Pastoral Appreciation Notes, 1949-1950 (Box 35)
  - Pastor's Book Account, undated (Box 35)
  - Patterson, J. Will, 1962-1968 (Box 35)
  - Payne, Betty, 1973-1975 (Box 35)
  - Payne, Robert L., 1954-1966 (Box 35)
  - Peace But Not Yet (Best Sermons) 1966 (Box 35)
  - Peacock, Heber F., 1959-1978 (Box 35)
  - Peal, M. E., 1958-1966 (Box 35)
  - Pearce, William E., 1966 (Box 35)
  - Pemberton, Prentiss L., 1959-1965 (Box 35)
  - Personalities of the South, 1973 (Box 36)
  - Phillips, Evelyn, 1962-1964 (Box 36)
  - Phillips, Fran, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Phillips, Rachel, 1958-1959 (Box 36)
  - Philosophy Discussion Group, 1952-1972 (Box 36)
  - Pickens, H.D., 1958-1960 (Box 36)
  - Pickens, Marshall I., 1964-1965 (Box 36)
  - Pitzer, Robert M., 1958-1964 (Box 36)
  - Placement, Ministerial, 1963-1976 (Box 36)
  - Placement, Miscellaneous, 1963-1966 (Box 36)
  - Poerschke, Robert E., 1959-1966 (Box 36)
  - Pollard, J. C., 1954-1975 (Box 36)
  - Potts, Dorothy, 1973-1974 (Box 36)
  - Potts, Hal, 1961-1977 (Box 36)
  - Pressly, Henry E., 1965-1977 (Box 36)
  - Preston, Jay W., 1958-1968 (Box 36)
  - Price, Richard E., Jr., 1958-1967 (Box 36)
  - Price, Sterling L., 1959-1968 (Box 36)
  - Price, Theron D., 1958-1964 (Box 37)
  - Prince, Suzanne, 1959-1963 (Box 37)
  - Property, Provence Road, Charlotte, 1958-1966 (Box 37)
  - Prophater, Dot, 1964-1971 (Box 37)
  - Pruden, Edward Huges, 1961-1967 (Box 37)
  - Public Affairs Committee, 1959-1963 (Box 37)
  - Puckett, Robert M., 1964-1977 (Box 37)
  - Pusey, Nathan M., 1961-1963 (Box 37)
  - Q. 1958-1978 (Box 37)
  - Queens-Charlotte Leadership Program, 1958-1960 (Box 37)
  - Quenelle, Fred W., 1958-1968 (Box 37)
  - Quinius, Henry W., Jr., 1958-1960 (Box 37)
  - Ra-Rd, 1958-1977 (Box 37)
  - Re-Rn, 1958-1977 (Box 37)
  - Ro-Rt, 1958-1978 (Box 37)
  - Ru-Rz, 1958-1977 (Box 37)
  - Raines, Robert A., 1974-1975 (Box 38)
  - Ramsay, John G., 1963-1969 (Box 38)
  - Ramsey, Brooks, 1973-1975 (Box 38)
  - Rankin, W. S., 1960-1969 (Box 38)
  - Ranson, Guy, 1954-1975 (Box 38)
  - Rawlinson, J. E., 1959-1961 (Box 38)
  - Ray, Willie E., 1975-1977 (Box 38)
  - Reddy, T.J., 1969-1977 (Box 38)
  - Reece, Thomas L., 1967-1968 (Box 38)
  - Reed, Donald C., 1975-1978 (Box 38)
  - Reese, Fred M., Jr., 1967-1971 (Box 38)
  - Reference and Recommendation Letters, 1961-1966 (Box 38)
  - The Reformed Hope (Church of the Nazarene Herald) 1963 (Box 38)
  - Reid, A. C., 1953-1966 (Box 39)
  - Reigner Recording Library, 1974-1977 (Box 39)
  - Religious Book Club, 1966 (Box 39)
  - Reville, Frances, 1958-1973 (Box 39)
  - Reynolds, Ralph W., 1965 (Box 39)
  - Rhodes, Lewis E., 1966-1975 (Box 39)
  - Richardson, Ted, 1961-1967 (Box 39)
  - Richardson, Vernon, 1959-1966 (Box 39)
  - Richey, McMurry S., 1959-1978 (Box 39)
  - Riffe, David, 1964 (Box 39)
  - Rivers, Ann, 1964-1975 (Box 39)
  - Roach, Ruth, 1967-1975 (Box 39)
  - Roach Tom, 1966 (Box 39)
  - Roden, William H., 1961-1965 (Box 39)
  - Rogers, Barry, 1968-1971 (Box 39)
  - Rogers, H. Levy, 1966-1967 (Box 39)
  - Rose, W. H., 1959-1960 (Box 39)
  - Ross, Otho B., 1959-1974 (Box 39)
  - Rossman, Parker, 1967 (Box 39)
  - Rottgerring, Blanche, 1959-1963 (Box 39)
  - Rousseau, G. J., 1954-1964 (Box 39)
  - Routh, E. C., 1958-1960 (Box 39)
  - Rowe, Robert L., 1963-1965 (Box 39)
  - Royder, Thomas, 1959-1971 (Box 39)
  - Rugheimer, John P., 1964-1969 (Box 39)
  - Sa-She, 1954-1978 (Box 40)
  - Shi-Sl, 1959-1978 (Box 40)
  - Sm-Ss, 1954-1978 (Box 40)
  - Sta-Sto, 1954-1978 (Box 40)
  - Str-Sz, 1959-1977 (Box 40)
  - Sales, Rev. Lyman, 1960-1966 (Box 41)
  - Sales, Lyman, Jr., 1961-1971 (Box 41)
  - Sanders, Phillip Eugene, 1958-1965 (Box 41)
  - Sanders, R. N., 1961-1963 (Box 41)
  - Sanks, Rev. C. R., Jr., 1959-1968 (Box 41)
  - Sapp, James M., 1949-1976 (Box 41)
  - Sargent, Robert E., 1959-1974 (Box 41)
  - Saunders, Rod, 1975-1978 (Box 41)
  - Savory, Jerold J., 1960 (Box 41)
  - Scarborough, Jerry P., 1958-1960 (Box 41)
  - Scarritt College, 1972-1973 (Box 41)
  - Schloss, S. A. Jr., 1965-1968 (Box 41)
  - Scholl, Tom, 1975 (Box 41)
  - Schroeder, Andrew, 1965-1966 (Box 41)
  - Schwantes, William L., 1960-1976 (Box 41)
  - Sermon Requests, 1954-1967, 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Seymour, Robert, 1961-1977 (Box 41)
  - Shaw University, 1960-1961 (Box 42)
  - Shearman, Winslow Ted, 1962-1967 (Box 42)
  - Shelton, R. Page, 1967-1969 (Box 42)
  - Shipman, L. J., 1959-1961 (Box 42)
  - Short, Harold, Sr., 1958-1964 (Box 42)
  - Short, Mrs. H. Milton, Jr., 1960-1975 (Box 42)
  - Shrader, Wesley, 1959-1967 (Box 42)
  - Siefferman, Norman, 1977 (Box 42)
  - Simpson, Robert, 1959-1966 (Box 42)
  - Singleton, Martha, 1966-1971 (Box 42)
  - Smith, Ann, 1961-1973 (Box 42)
  - Smith, Blake, 1958-1974, 2 folders (Box 42)
  - Smith, Dottie Ann, 1958-1959 (Box 42)
  - Smith, Edward James, Jr., 1958-1968 (Box 43)
  - Smith, Helen, 1959-1960 (Box 43)
  - Smith, Jack Glen, 1959-1962 (Box 43)
  - Smith, John Lee, 1958-1974 (Box 43)
  - Smith, Mike, 1961-1975 (Box 43)
  - Smith, T. C., 1962-1966 (Box 43)
  - Smucker, Donovan E., 1958-1970 (Box 43)
  - Snider, David J., 1961-1971 (Box 43)
  - Southwestern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1957-1960 (Box 43)
  - Sparkman, G. Temp, 1974-1977 (Box 43)
  - Sparks, Ron B., 1973 (Box 43)
  - Spaugh, Herbert, 1960-1970 (Box 43)
  - Speakman, Fred, 1966-1975 (Box 43)
  - Spencer, John B., 1958-1960 (Box 43)
  - Springfield, Thaxton, 1969-1970 (Box 43)
  - Stagg, Paul E., 1959 (Box 43)
  - Staples, George, 1960-1961 (Box 43)
  - Steakley, Zollie, 1958-1977 (Box 43)
  - Stealey, Snydnor L., 1958-1970 (Box 43)
  - Stembridge, Hensel H., 1958-1977 (Box 44)
  - Stembridge, Jane Shelton, 1959-1977 (Box 44)
  - Stephens, F. Dwight, Jr., 1960-1966 (Box 44)
  - Stephens, Nita, 1963-1967 (Box 44)
  - Stickley, John L., 1958-1967 (Box 44)
  - Stitt, David L., 1958-1967 (Box 44)
  - Stowe, Charles, 1961-1966 (Box 44)
  - Stuart, R. Marvin, 1968-1976 (Box 44)
  - Suggs, David and Jean Ann, 1974-1978 (Box 44)
  - Sumner, Lee, 1959-1968 (Box 44)
  - The Sunday School Board, 1962-1964 (Box 44)
  - Sutherland, W. S., 1959-1976 (Box 44)
  - Swain, Leslie E., 1960 (Box 44)
  - Swanzey, Henry, 1958-1967 (Box 44)
  - Swindelle, Faye Wiess, 1961-1968 (Box 44)
  - Swink, David, 1974-1977 (Box 44)
  - Swope, George W., 1959-1960 (Box 44)
  - Sykes, John M., 1961-1973 (Box 44)
  - T-Th, 1959-1974 (Box 45)
  - Ti-Tz, 1954-1978 (Box 45)
  - Tabscott, Robert W., 1966-1976 (Box 45)
  - Taylor, James E., 1960-1966 (Box 45)
  - Television Program Letters, 1953-1959 (Box 45)
  - Terrill, Tom E., 1961-1978 (Box 45)
  - Terry, John V., 1958 (Box 45)
  - Texas Quarterly, 1958 (Box 45)
  - Theology Today Editorial Board, 1970-1977 (Box 45)
  - Thomas, Everett, 1966-1977 (Box 45)
  - Thompson, J. Earl, 1960-1963 (Box 45)
  - Thompson, J. Earl, Jr., 1959-1964 (Box 45)
  - Thompson, Luther Joe, 1958-1965 (Box 45)
  - Thompson, Stella Green, 1954-1961 (Box 45)
  - Thompson, Sydnor, 1968-1970 (Box 45)
  - Thoughts for Meditation, 1962-1977 (Box 45)
  - Todaro, Samuel P., 1966-1978 (Box 46)
  - Tompkins, Jerry R., 1954-1966 (Box 46)
  - Tompkins, Leslie C., 1961 (Box 46)
  - Toward Judah 1968-1969 (Box 46)
  - Tracey, Nat, 1962-1975 (Box 46)
  - Trent, B.C., 1961-1973 (Box 46)
  - Trentham, Charles A., 1958-1977 (Box 46)
  - Tribble, Harold W., 1958-1976 (Box 46)
  - Trip to South America, 1951 (Box 46)
  - Trotter, Syd, 1958-1977 (Box 46)
  - Troutman, Colt R. Jr., 1961-1966 (Box 46)
  - The True Believer 1968-1976 (Box 46)
  - Trueblood, D. Elton, 1959-1973 (Box 46)
  - Tucker, E.J., 1954-1963 (Box 46)
  - Tullis, Roland, 1972 (Box 46)
  - Tyson, Joseph B., 1962-1975 (Box 46)
  - U. 1971-1974 (Box 46)
  - U. S. Office of Education, Special Programs Branch (Box 46)
  - University of Glasgow, 1975-1976 (Box 46)
  - Upchurch, Priscilla, 1958-1970 (Box 46)
  - V, 1958-1976 (Box 47)
  - Valentine, Foy, 1958-1965 (Box 47)
  - Vanderbeck, H. John, 1960-1966 (Box 47)
  - Vayhinger, John M., 1969-1972 (Box 47)
  - A Very Reverent Synthesis (McCormick Quarterly) 1963 (Box 47)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1974-1977 (Box 47)
  - Wa-Wd, 1958-1976 (Box 47)
  - We-Wh, 1958-1976 (Box 47)
  - Wi-Wil, 1958-1978 (Box 47)
  - Wim-Wz, 1954-1977 (Box 48)
  - Wade, Linda, 1975-1977 (Box 48)
  - Wake Forest College, 1958-1967 (Box 48)
  - Walker, Aubrey, 1964-1965 (Box 48)
  - Walker, Jerald C., 1968-1973 (Box 48)
  - Walker, Joy, 1964-1974 (Box 48)
  - Wall, Margaret, 1959-1975 (Box 48)
  - Wallace, Doris J., 1966 (Box 48)
  - Walters, Dean E., 1977-1978 (Box 48)
  - Walters, George, 1960-1963 (Box 48)
  - Wamble, Hugh, 1958-1967 (Box 48)
  - Ward, Clara M., 1959-1961 (Box 48)
  - Ware, Browning, 1961-1976 (Box 48)
  - Ware, Weston W., 1961-1962 (Box 48)
  - Warren, Virgil, 1974-1975 (Box 48)
  - Watkins, Basil M., Jr., 1959-1961 (Box 48)
  - Watson, Jerry W., 1962-1963 (Box 48)
  - Weatherley, Owen, 1959-1976 (Box 48)
  - Weathers, R.L., 1959-1967 (Box 48)
  - Weatherspoon, J.P., 1958-1959 (Box 48)
  - Webb, W. Guy, 1967-1978 (Box 48)
  - Webster, C. A., Jr., 1959-1968 (Box 48)
  - Weddington, Diane, 1974-1977 (Box 49)
  - Weiant, Ted, 1971-1977 (Box 49)
  - Welchel, Michael, 1966-1970 (Box 49)
  - Weldon, Wilson O., 1959-1975 (Box 49)
  - Wellford, Sue, 1963-1966 (Box 49)
  - Welsh, Robert B., 1961-1973 (Box 49)
  - Wertz, James, 1961-1971 (Box 49)
  - Wesley Foundation Campus Ministry at SUNY Buffalo, 1977 (Box 49)
  - Whaley, Harvey, 1961-1967 (Box 49)
  - When Wisdom Flirts with Madness 1968 (Box 49)
  - White, W. D., 1968-1970 (Box 49)
  - Who's Who in America, 1965-1976 (Box 49)
  - Wilkie, Le Roy, 1964-1968 (Box 49)
  - Wilkshire, Robert A., 1973 (Box 49)
  - Williams, Daniel Day, 1963-1969 (Box 49)
  - Williams, Jerome O., 1960-1974 (Box 49)
  - Williams, John, 1967-1970 (Box 49)
  - Williams, Samuel S., 1966-1971 (Box 49)
  - Williamson, George, 1961-1964 (Box 49)
  - Williamson, George Jr., 1966-1976 (Box 49)
  - Wilmith Hospital, 1963-1965 (Box 49)
  - Wilmot, Ruth E., 1966-1971 (Box 49)
  - Wilson, Jeff D., 1974-1978 (Box 49)
  - Wilson, W. Jake, 1960 (Box 49)
  - Wingate College, 1958 -1964 (Box 50)
  - Winthrop College, 1960 (Box 50)
  - Wisely, Allie D., 1959-1962 (Box 50)
  - Wiseman, William J., 1969-1977 (Box 50)
  - Wofford, Adams, 1966-1975 (Box 50)
  - Women's Missionary Society, 1958-1960 (Box 50)
  - Woodruff, C. Roy, 1960-1977 (Box 50)
  - Worcester, Ben D., 1960-1975 (Box 50)
  - World Council of Churches, 1954-1963 (Box 50)
  - Worthy, Charles I., 1972-1974 (Box 50)
  - Wuertenberger, Anna, 1964-1966 (Box 50)
  - Y. 1958-1977 (Box 50)
  - Yates, Kyle M., 1961-1967 (Box 50)
  - Young, Franklin W., 1963-1969 (Box 50)
  - Z. 1958-1966 (Box 50)
  - Anonymous, 1949-1978 (Box 51)
  - Anonymous, no date (Box 51)
- Writings and Speeches Series, 1930-1978 and undated
  Published and unpublished material, including handwritten, typed, mimeographed and printed items, such as reprints, pamphlets, and clippings. Includes sermons, speeches, lectures, and addresses, and manuscripts for books and articles. Arranged in two divisions: writings of Marney and writings of others.
  Marney's writings are arranged chronologically, and besides publication drafts and sermons, includes some scattered correspondence and book reviews. When several items pertain to one title, they are filed together under the date of the earliest item. Undated items have been organized alphabetically by title. An alphabetical index to iitles of Marney's works that are found in the Writings and Speeches Series can be found at the end of the box inventory in this collection guide.
  The Writings of Others subseries includes some prayers and anonymous writings. This category is organized alphabetically by the last name of the author; anonymous works are at the end.
  - Writings by Carlyle Marney
    - 1942, Apr.-1950, Feb., 5 folders (Box 52)
    - 1950, Mar.-1951, Apr., 4 folders (Box 53)
    - 1951, May-1952, Dec., 8 folders (Box 54)
    - Great Encounters Part I-III, 1952 (notes 2 folders) (Box 55)
    - Great Encounters Part II and III, 1952 (Box 55)
    - Great Encounters Part I, 1952 (Copy 2 and 3, 2 folders) (Box 55)
    - Great Encounters Part I and II, 1952 (Copy 4, incomplete) 1953, 3 folders (Box 55)
    - These Things Remain, (Notes, 2 folders), 1953 (Box 56)
    - These Things Remain, ( Is There No Peace), 1953 (Box 56)
    - These Things Remain, (Page Proofs, 2 folders), 1953 (Box 56)
    - These Things Remain, (Printers Proof), 1953 (Box 56)
    - These Things Remain, (Galley Proofs), 1953 (Box 56)
    - 1954, 3 folders (Box 57)
    - City of Light (Notes), 1954, 2 folders (Box 57)
    - City of Light (Introduction), 1954 (Box 57)
    - City of Light (Part I, Chap. 1-6), 1954, 6 folders (Box 57)
    - City of Light (Chap. 7-9), 1954, 3 folders (Box 58)
    - City of Light (Chap. 1-9), 1954, 2 folders (Box 58)
    - City of Light (Given as Sermons), 1954-1956) (Box 58)
    - City of Light (Chap. 1-9 Corrected), 1954, 2 folders (Box 58)
    - City of Light (Part I, Copy 1), 1954 (Box 58)
    - City of Light (Part II and III, Copy 1), 1954 (Box 59)
    - City of Light (Part I-III Copy 2), 1954, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - City of Light (Harper Brothers Publishers), 1954 (Box 59)
    - City of Light (Judson Press), 1954 (Box 59)
    - City of Light (MacMillan Co. Publishers), 1954 (Box 59)
    - City of Light...City of Wilderness, 1954 (Box 59)
    - City in the Wilderness (Chap. 1-12), 1954, 2 folders (Box 59)
    - City in the Wilderness (Chap. 1-12, Copy 2 and 3), 1954, 4 folders (Box 60)
    - 1955, Jan.-Aug., 2 folders (Box 60)
    - 1955, Sept.-1956 Dec., 6 folders (Box 61)
    - 1957, 3 folders (Box 62)
    - Faith in Conflict, 1957 (Box 62)
    - 1958, Jan.-May, 2 folders (Box 62)
    - 1958, June-Dec., 2 folders (Box 63)
    - The Most Tragic Man (Part I-V) 1958, 3 folders (Box 63)
    - Tragic Man - Tragic House (Notes), 1958, 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Tragic Man - Tragic House (Notes), 1958 (Box 64)
    - Tragic Man - Tragic House (Typed, incomplete), 1958 (Box 64)
    - Tragic Man - Tragic House (Chap. 1-20), 1958, 3 folders (Box 64)
    - 1959 (Box 65)
    - Faith and the Falcon, lecture draft, 1950s (Box 148)
      Scope and Contents